Do you ever find yourself looking for different ways to entertain yourself?
Hi, my name is Dean Hale, I'm going to tell you a little bit about how to play dice.
Dice is a pretty old game, and it's been played throughout the ages.
You can play it in many different forms and fashions, sometimes you use the dice to play board games, sometimes you use it at casinos to play what they call craps.
You could use the dice in various fashions, six could actually be a six.
It could also correspond to something on a board or the game you're playing that may mean something else.
You could the numbers, and if you're trying to make a poker hand, for example, you could have the one, count as an ace.
A two as a two, you could try to make straights, you could try to make full houses, a full house is something where you have let's say, two sixes, along with three fives.
That would be fives over sixes and you could have that with dice also.
Dice are typically square shaped, six sided, and as you roll them, they'll come out and the numbers will come out on the top.
It is the top number how you count the dice, you would not look at anything from the sides, it would actually be the top.
Most people understand that, but just to make sure, you are counting the top dice.
When you roll your dice, you have to take them in your hand and move them around so everybody knows you're not just putting down a number and turning it over.
So you would roll your dice, shake them in your hand, and then roll them and whatever the number came up with, or whatever game you were playing, that's how it would be used.
Now you can be created when you're playing dice.
You can come up with any kind of different games.
You can do something with your children, help them learn how to count, you could say, roll the dice and ask your daughter what's two plus two.
You could have her say four, and an easy way is have her count the pips on the dice and that could be a fun way to do some learning at home.
There's many different things you can do with dice, I suggest you go out there, use your imagination, and have a good time.
My name is Dean Hale, and I've just taught you how to play dice.